eataly.it 2015-06-01

# Privacy Policy

**PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA ON EATALY NET**

**What is A Privacy Policy?**

This information is provided - [**also in pursuance of Section 13 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003**](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/garante/document?ID=1219452) -  to any entity having to do with the web-based services that are made available by Eataly Net S.r.l via electronic networks as from the following address:

_www.eataly.net_

which corresponds to the home page of our official web site.

The information provided only applies to our web site and does not concern any web sites that may be visited by an user via external links.

The information provided is also based on the guidelines contained in Recommendation no. 2/2001, which was adopted on 17 May 2001 by the European data protection authorities within the Working Party set up under [**Article 29 of European Directive 95/46/EC**](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/garante/document?ID=432175) in order to lay down minimum requirements for the collection of personal data online - especially with regard to arrangements, timing and contents of the information to be provided by data controllers to users visiting web pages for whatever purpose.

**Data Controller**

Visiting this site may result into the processing of data concerning identified or identifiable persons.

The data controller Mr. Franco Denari,while the data processor is Eataly Net S.r.l. with registered office in Monticello d’Alba S.S. 231, Zona Industriale n. 2 (CN), CAP 12066, VAT n.: 03453380044

**Place Where Data Is Processed**

The processing operations related to the web-based services that are made available via this website are carried out at the aforementioned office of Eataly Net exclusively by technical staff in charge of said processing, or else by persons tasked with such maintenance activities as may be necessary from time to time.

No data resulting from web-based services is either communicated or disseminated.

Any personal data that is provided by users requesting to be sent information materials such as bulletins, CD-ROMs, newsletters, annual reports, answers to questions, decisions and sundry provisions, etc. is only used to provide the service and/or discharge the tasks requested and is disclosed to third parties only if this is necessary for the said purposes. Personal data entered by users are collected and managed electronically by the company or delgated third parties for the following purposes: purposes related to accessing communication information shown on [http://shop.eataly](http://shop.eataly/) and related websites. In any case your data will not be exchanged or sold to third parties (except for posting companies and data entry companies). Within Eataly Net S.r.l. data will be accessible solely by specifically designated people working within the administrative department. ****

  **Categories of Processed Data**

_Navigation Data_

The information systems and software procedures relied upon to operate this web site acquire personal data as part of their standard functioning; the transmission of such data is an inherent feature of Internet communication protocols.

Such information is not collected in order to relate it to identified data subjects, however it might allow user identification per se after being processed and matched with data held by third parties.

This data category includes IP addresses and/or the domain names of the computers used by any user connecting with this web site, the URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) addresses of the requested resources, the time of such requests, the method used for submitting a given request to the server, returned file size, a numerical code relating to server response status (successfully performed, error, etc.), and other parameters related to the user's operating system and computer environment.

These data are only used to extract statistical information on website use as well as to check its functioning. The data might be used to establish liability in case computer crimes are committed against the website; except for this circumstance, any data on web contacts is currently retained for no longer than seven days.

_Data Provided Voluntarily by Users_

Sending e-mail messages to the addresses mentioned on this website, which is done on the basis of a freely chosen, explicit, and voluntary option, entails acquisition of the sender's address, which is necessary in order to reply to any request, as well as of such additional personal data as is contained in the message(s).

Specific summary information notices will be shown and/or displayed on the pages that are used for providing services on demand.

_Cookies_

No personal data concerning users is acquired by the website in this regard.

No cookies are used to transmit personal information, nor are so-called persistent cookies or user tracking systems implemented.

Use of the so-called session cookies – which are not stored permanently on the user's computer and disappear upon closing the browser – is exclusively limited to the transmission of session ID's – consisting of server-generated casual numbers – as necessary to allow secure, effective navigation.

The so-called session cookies used by this website make it unnecessary to implement other computer techniques that are potentially detrimental to the confidentiality of user navigation, whilst they do not allow acquiring the user's personal identification data.

Eataly Net works along with other companies which lay cookies or beacons on our websites. The service providers contribute to the functioning of our websites, by compiling meaasurements, anonimous analyses, pertaining the website or the provision of advertising services. The afore-mentioned companies are obliged to use the collected information solely for the above mentioned services and by no means for commercial ends.

**Optional Data Provision**

Subject to the specifications made with regard to navigation data, users are free to provide the personal data either to be entered in the application forms submitted to Eataly Net or referred to in contacting Eataly Net to request delivery of information materials and other communications.

Failure to provide such data may entail the failure to be provided with the items requested.

**  Processing Arrangements**

Personal data is processed with automated means for no longer than is necessary to achieve the purposes for which it has been collected.

Specific security measures are implemented to prevent the data from being lost, used unlawfully and/or inappropriately, and accessed without authorisation. ****

**Data Subjects' Rights**

Data subjects are entitled at any time to obtain confirmation of the existence of personal data concerning them and be informed of their contents and origin, verify their accuracy, or else request that such data be supplemented, updated or rectified ([ **Section 7 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003**](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/garante/document?ID=1219452)).

The above Section also provides for the right to request erasure, anonymisation or blocking of any data that is processed in breach of the law as well as to object in all cases, on legitimate grounds, to processing of the data.

All requests should be addressed to Eataly Net S.r.l. , Monticello d’Alba S.S. 231 Zona Industriale n. 2 (CN) CAP 12066, Italy VAT no.: 03453380044 or via fax to 0173/228167
